// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "On a scale of 1 to 10, how stressful is your day?",
    answer: "A. Less than 5",
    options: [
      "A. Less than 5",
      "B. More than 5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Are you noticing sudden weight gain?",
    answer: "B. No, I work really hard to manage it",
    options: [
      "A. Oh yes",
      "B. No, I work really hard to manage it",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Do you use hormonal birth control pills?",
    answer: "A. Yeah",
    options: [
      "A. Yeah",
      "B. No",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "	How often do you exercise?",
    answer: "B. Oh I’m a fitness freak",
    options: [
      "A. I’m not that regular",
      "B. Oh I’m a fitness freak",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Do your periods often go missing?",
    answer: "B. Thankfully, no",
    options: [
      "A. Sometimes",
      "B. Thankfully, no",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How long do your periods usually last?",
    answer: "A. 4 to 7 days",
    options: [
      "A. 4 to 7 days",
      "B. More than 7 days",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What about cramps – how bad do they get?",
    answer: "A.  Mild cramps right before it arrives and some pain during the first few days",
    options: [
      "A.   Mild cramps right before it arrives and some pain during the first few days",
      "B. SERIOUS pain, often the can’t get out of bed kind",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Do you have a sweet tooth?",
    answer: "A. Yes, big time",
    options: [
      "A. Yes, big time",
      "B. Not really",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Do you have pre-existing health issues?",
    answer: "B. No",
    options: [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How often do you get your period?",
    answer: "B. Like clockwork, every 28 to 30 days",
    options: [
      "A.  Sometimes it comes a week early or a week later",
      "B. Like clockwork, every 28 to 30 days",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "	What’s your sleep cycle like?",
    answer: "B. I sleep 7 to 8 hours a day",
    options: [
      "A. It’s very disrupted",
      "B. I sleep 7 to 8 hours a day",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question: " How long is your luteal phase?",
    answer: "B. 14 days, all time, every time. I have used it accurately to conceive and have been successful",
    options: [
      "A. My period is so irregular I never know",
      "B. 14 days, all time, every time. I have used it accurately to conceive and have been successful",
    ]
  },

];